allthebestfights.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy policy & Disclosure - All The Best Fights.com

By visiting and using <https://www.allthebestfights.com/> (the “Site”), you explicitly consent to such use of your information and agree to the Privacy Policy, Legal Notices and Terms of Use.

### PRIVACY POLICY

The privacy of our users is important to us and we have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain to you how we collect, use and share information we obtain through your use of the Site. 

#### What personal data we collect and why we collect it

Like all websites, this Site also makes use of ‘log files’ in which information are collected in an automated manner during user visits. The information collected could be the following: internet protocol (IP) address, type of browser and device parameters used to connect to the Site, name of the internet service provider (ISP), date and time of visit, language you speak, web page of the origin of the visitor (referral) and exit, possibly the number of clicks, etc. The information may be collected directly by us, or by a third-party website hosting provider, or another third-party service provider and we use such data to provide better services to all of our users. 

#### Information you provide to us

We may collect and store information that you choose to voluntarily provide to us when you contact us. Some examples of this type of personal information may include information that you electronically submit when you contact us with questions (name, email, telephone number) or participate in surveys or information that you post on comments and social networking areas on our Site. We use the information you provide to respond to your question or to communicate with you about other topics that we think may be of interest to you.

If you give us information about another person or third parties, you confirm that the other person has appointed you to act on their behalf and agreed that you: shall consent on their behalf to the processing of their personal data; shall receive any data protection notices on their behalf; and shall consent on their behalf to the transfer of their personal data abroad.

This information helps us to build a profile of our users. Some of this information may be aggregated or statistical, which means that we will not be able to identify you individually. In addition it should be noted that in some cases our cookies or similar technologies may be owned and controlled by third parties who will also collect personal information about you. On the first occasion that you use our site we will ask whether you consent to our use of cookies. If you do not, cookies will not be used. Thereafter you can opt-out of using cookies at any time or you can set your browser not to accept cookies and the websites below tell you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, some of our website features may not function as a result. For further information on our use of cookies, please see our Website cookie policy. For further information on cookies generally visit <https://www.aboutcookies.org/> or <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>.

#### How we use and share information we collect

We may use and share the information we collect from you while you are using the Site in different ways such as: to respond to questions or communications, to send you email, customizing features and advertising that appear on the Site, to measure Site traffic, to improve users’ experience or for any purpose related to the Site.  
We also may use and share your information with our affiliates or to third parties, including our third party service providers and contractors, for purposes related to Site administration and other services.  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies (Opt Out of Interest-Based Advertising), please visit the following link: <https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>  
The use and collection of information by third-party advertising companies is governed by the relevant third party’s privacy policy and is not covered by ours.  
We may share your information with law enforcement agencies in connection with any investigation to help prevent unlawful activity.

#### Comments

We use Disqus platform for the Site comments so if you need to read their privacy policy, you can find it here: <https://help.disqus.com/terms-and-policies/disqus-privacy-policy>  
If Disqus is not active and users leave comments on the Site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.  
An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

#### Media

If you upload images to the Site, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

#### Cookies

Cookies are small piece of data that is sent from a website and stored in a user’s web browser when he visits a website. We use cookies and other similar technologies on the Site for security purposes to gather statistical and geographical data, to display the most appropriate advertisements, to identify how many users visit us, to track your preferences, etc.  
Similar technologies include web beacons, action tags, local shared objects (‘flash cookies’) and single-pixel gifs. Such technologies can be used to track users’ actions and activities, and to store information about them. We use these cookies and/or similar technologies on this website. For example we may use cookies to monitor and/or collect the following information:  
preferences;  
security;  
processes;  
advertising;  
session state;  
analytics (determine which domain to measure, distinguish unique users, throttle the request rate, remember the number and time of previous visits, remember traffic source information, determine the start and end of a session, remember the value of visitor-level custom variables).

Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies but you can disable certain functionality or set certain privacy setting (through your browser) to refuse cookies. However if you want to limit the use of cookies, you may affect your website experience and may not be able to take full advantage of our Site.

Users can also manage cookies through the settings of their browser. However, deleting cookies from your browser may remove the preferences you have set for the Site. For further information and support, you can also visit the specific help page of the web browser you are using:  
Internet Explorer: <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies>  
Firefox: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-us/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>  
Safari: <https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411?>  
Chrome: <https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/61416>  
Opera: <http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/>

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.  
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.  
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.  
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

#### Analytics

We also use third-party web analytics services and providers of applications (such as Google Analytics or sharing buttons) that use cookies to help us to analyse how users use the Site and to collect information about visitor traffic. For more information about Google Analytics’ privacy policy, please refer to <https://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html>, or if you want to install the add-on for your browser to opt out of Google Analytics, please visit the following link: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl+en=GB>. 

This Site also incorporates plugins and / or buttons for social networks, in order to allow easy sharing of content on your favorite social networks. These plugins are programmed so as not to set any cookies when accessing the page, to safeguard the privacy of users. Possibly cookies are set, if so provided by social networks, only when the user makes effective and voluntary use of the plugin. Please note that if the user browses being logged into the social network then he has already consented to the use of cookies conveyed through this site at the time of registration to the social network.  
The collection and use of the information obtained by means of the plugin are governed by the respective privacy policies of the social networks, to which reference is made:  
Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/>  
Twitter: <https://help.twitter.com/en/rules-and-policies/twitter-cookies>  
Google+: <http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/cookies>  
WhatsApp: <https://www.whatsapp.com/legal/>  
AddThis: <http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy>

#### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this Site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.  
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

#### Links

Our Site includes links to other websites and provides access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we do not control. In this case we are not responsible for the privacy notice of other website you are visiting or the provider of such products or services.

#### How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.  
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

#### How we protect your data and where we send your data

We have appropriate security measures in place to prevent personal information from being accidentally lost, or used or accessed in an unauthorised way. We limit access to your personal information to those who have a genuine business need to know it. Those processing your information will do so only in an authorised manner and are subject to a duty of confidentiality. We will also use technological and organisation measures to keep your information secure.  
We also have procedures in place to deal with any suspected data security breach. We will notify you and any applicable regulator of a suspected data security breach where we are legally required to do so.  
Indeed, while we will use all reasonable efforts to secure your personal data, in using the site you acknowledge that the use of the internet is not entirely secure and for this reason we cannot guarantee the security or integrity of any personal data that are transferred from you or to you via the internet. If you have any particular concerns about your information, please contact us.

We may need to transfer your personal data outside of the European Economic Area because our database and website is hosted in the USA and we use third parties that can use cookies and other similar technologies on the Site for security purposes to gather statistical and geographical data, to display the most appropriate advertisements, to identify how many users visit us, to track your preferences, etc.

Any transfers outside of the European Economic Area will be undertaken on the basis that that country, territory or one or more specific sectors in that country, or an international organisation ensures an adequate level of protection.  
For more information on the basis of any non-EEA transfers, our safeguards or Commission details, please contact us as described below. We will not otherwise transfer your personal data outside of the EEA or to any organisation (or subordinate bodies) governed by public international law or which is set up under any agreement between two or more countries.

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. 

#### What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. 

Under the General Data Protection Regulation you have a number of important rights free of charge. In summary, those include rights to:  
fair processing of information and transparency over how we use your use personal information;  
access to your personal information and to certain other supplementary information that this Privacy Notice is already designed to address;  
require us to correct any mistakes in your information which we hold;  
require the erasure of personal information concerning you in certain situations;  
receive the personal information concerning you which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and have the right to transmit those data to a third party in certain situations;  
object at any time to processing of personal information concerning you for direct marketing;  
object to decisions being taken by automated means which produce legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect you;  
object in certain other situations to our continued processing of your personal information;  
otherwise restrict our processing of your personal information in certain circumstances;  
claim compensation for damages caused by our breach of any data protection laws.

For further informaiton on each of those rights, including the circumstances in which they apply, see the Guidance from the UK Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) on individual’s rights under the General Data Protection Regulations (<http://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/>)

If you would like to exercise any of these rights please:  
email, call or write to us;  
let us have enough information to identify you;  
let us have proof of your identity (a copy of your driving license, passport or a recent credit card/utility bill);  
let us know the information to which your request relates.

#### How to complain

We hope that we can resolve any query or concern you raise about our use of your information.

The General Data Protection Regulation also gives you right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the European Union (or European Economic Area) state where you work, normally live or where any alleged infringement of data protection laws occurred. The supervisory authority in the UK is the Information Commissioner who may be contacted at <https://ico.org.uk/concerns/> or telephone: 0303 123 1113.

### LEGAL NOTICES – WHO WE ARE

The Site is edited by Garbolino Alberto Daniel (editor-in-chief) – promenade Reine Astrid 5, 06500 Menton, France – info(at)allthebestfights.com, 00393497705322 – N° SIRET: 81256738600014 RCS Nice – TVA intracommunautaire: FR20812567386 – CNIL: 1899319 v 0 – Web hosting: Linode LLC, 249 Arch St. Philadelphia, PA 19106, USA, +1 609-380-7100

### TERMS OF USE

By using AllTheBestFights.com (the “Site) you agree to be bound by these Terms of Use, our Privacy Policy, Legal Notices and any additional terms and conditions that are referenced herein or that may apply to specific sections of the Site, or to products and services that you can find on the Site.  
You agree that we may use and share any information that we collect about you in accordance with our Privacy Policy.  
In addition, you agree that you are solely responsible for all of your User Submissions and we may refuse to display, host and approve them. We are not responsible for the content, messages, information, links or files that you or other users may post or provide on our website. You represent and warrant that your User Submissions do not and will not violate any law or regulation; transmit any abusive, defamatory, vulgar, pornographic material; transmit any unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, junk mail or spam; transmit any material that contains adware, malware, spyware, software viruses, or any other computer files designed to limit the functionality of any software or hardware; use any “robot, “spider” or any other data-mining technology or process to monitor, cache, frame, mask, extract data from, copy or distribute any data from the Site. You grant to us to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate and publicly display your User Submissions (in whole or in part) on our Site.  
We reserve the right to display advertisements (targeted or not) in connection with User Submissions and using the Site you agree that we may place such advertisements throughout our website.

#### Disclaimer, Trademarks rights and Copyright infringement

You expressly agree that use of the Site is at your sole risk as well as any material or information downloaded or otherwise obtained through the use of the Site is done at your own discretion and risk. In addition, AllTheBestFights.com shall not be liable for any errors, inaccuracies, omissions or other defects in the information contained within the Site. 

All the names of companies, images, screenshots, videos and trademarks of third parties mentioned on this website are used for information and review purposes (and are property of their respective owners). None of the videos are hosted by our servers and we post just free embeddable videos or gif hosted on free and public external website such as Youtube, Dailymotion, Vimeo, Streamable, Sapo, Youku, Rutube, Spruto etc. So if you find a video that you want to report, please contact the website where the video is hosted. Otherwise if you believe that any other material (not video) is being used somewhere on the Site in a way that constitutes trademark or copyright infringement, you should contact us at info(at)allthebestfights.com.

The Site design, name, logo, rankings and all written content are © copyright of AllTheBestFights.com and are protected by copyright, trademark, and other intellectual property laws. The Site is provided only for your personal non-commercial use and you may not use, modify, copy, reproduce, republish, post, transmit, translate or sell any material we produce if it has not been authorized by us. 

#### Changes to the privacy policy

This privacy policy was published on January 19, 2011 and last updated on May 20, 2018.

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. You should check this policy occasionally to ensure you are aware of the most recent version that will apply each time you access this website. We will also attempt to notify users of any changes by a notice on the website header.

﻿
